

Berk Disli

Full Stack Web Developer

Page Berlin, 10179 Germany berkdisli@yahoo.com +491638614308

Profile

Passionate full stack developer, trained in back-end and front-end development. Experienced in engineering and social media industries. Skilled atdesigning, web development, debugging and modifying websites, apps and mobile applications.

Linkedin - GitHub - Portfolio - Medium

Holding working permit in Germany and will not need any visa support.

Education

Aug 2021 — Mar 2022

Berlin/Germany

Sep 2011 — Jun

2016

Istanbul/Turkey

CareerFoundry

Full Stack Web Development program helps students build API, web and mobile applications. Skills to design and build databases for software applications, create and deploy web API, secure and manage user authentication, to deploy web applications to the cloud. Here is the link to the detailed curriculum of the program.

Isik University

Biomedical Engineering

The program covers fundamental topics of electrical and electronics engineering along with core biomedical engineering courses on systems, physiology, biomaterials, biomechanics, bioinstrumentation, bio-signal processing, medical imaging and bioinformatics.

Development **Projects**

Web and Mobile Applications

Pokédex API: List of Pokémons

• The web application is designed to provide an overview of all the Pokémon characters.

Tools: jQuery, Bootstrap

Chit-Chat: A chat app

• Chit-Chat is a mobile application for fast communication between end users.

Tools: React Native, Expo, GiftedChat, NetInfo

To-Do-List App

Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React

Angular

Redux

React Native

*i*Ouery

Bootstrap

GiftedChat

MongoDB

Jest

Node.js

Languages

English

German

Turkish

 A basic to-do-list app allowing users to add and delete to-dos, edit and mark them as completed.

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Meet App: List of developers' events

• The web application is used to see the upcoming events which are set up in Google Calendar.

Tools: React, Jest, Google Calendar API

Movie App: MyFlix

 The website is designed to show the retrieved film data and enable a user profile section. Functions such as logging in, logging out, registering and de-registering users are also integrated.

Tools: React-Bootstrap, Netlify, MongoDB

Tools: Angular, MongoDB

Employment History

Social Media Specialist, Majorel, Berlin 01.2021 - present

- Responsible for evaluating online social media content (images, videos, text, etc.), showed in the social media app
- Removal of inappropriate content in order to ensure a safe experience for users of the application and community
- · Maintain a high level of quality in each case

Social Media Specialist, Conectys, Istanbul 11.2018 - 02.2020

- Screened, monitored, and approved social media content
- Moderated videos, audio clips and comments in German market for a well-known company

Field Service Engineer, Medisa, Istanbul 01.2016 - 11.2016

- Designed, tested and implemented new medical procedures as well as modified products, equipment and devices
- Trained staff to use equipment safely and properly
- · Wrote technical reports and documentation